{
    "id": "1464bfef823046abbb5b4091727d75be",
    "title": "Review: Present perfect tense",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ecf2acf418be4294838bade8019c8afa",
            "title": "Present Perfect Tense",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He ........................................ to all the continents in the world.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "has been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have never ............................................ a ghost.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "saw",
                        "seen",
                        "see"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ............................................... experienced despair.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have",
                        "was"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .......................................... that movie.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has seen",
                        "saw",
                        "have seen"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .............................................. all the novels written by Mark Twain.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "am read",
                        "have read",
                        "had read"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ......................................... faced many setbacks in life.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ................................................. written a novel.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Raju ................................................. played cricket at the national level.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ........................................... seen her before.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .............................................. that movie.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "watched",
                        "have watched",
                        "has watched"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}